<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed>
	<seasons>
		<season>
			<victim name="Brian Moser" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/moser.png"  polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/moserColor.png" primary="true">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Brian Moser (aka Rudy Cooper) "The Ice Truck Killer"<br>
						1970 - 2006
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[You're the one who needs freeing, little brother.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"You're the one who needs freeing, little brother."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO BRIAN/RUDY WAS:</h3>
						<p>Prosthetics Specialist, Brother, Son, Fiance, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Brian/Rudy was the infamous Ice Truck Killer (and he used Dexter's sister Debra to get to Dexter). If anyone deserved it, he did. Ironically, of all Dexter's victims, Brian/Rudy was the only one Dexter wanted to let go. Why? He was Dexter's biological brother. Together, they witnessed the brutal murder of their mother. Brian/Rudy was the only one who could really understand Dexter but Harry's code outweighed Dexter's need to connect. Also, he refused to choose Brian/Rudy over his adopted sister, Debra.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>BRIAN/RUDY'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Killed, dismembered, beheaded, and exsanguinated several prostitutes, including Sheri Taylor and Monique, the one-handed hooker. Killed his and Dexter's father, Joe Driscoll. Killed Driscoll's elderly neighbor, Irma Holt. Maimed Tony Tucci.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>The Ice Truck Killer (ITK) left a dismembered Barbie doll in Dexter's freezer. (Ep. 1) She had multi-colored painted fingernails, just like the fingertips found in the block of ice (Ep. 2). Ultimately, Dexter remembered that his mother painted her fingernails that way.<br></p>
						<p>The ITK perused Dexter's personal photo albums and recreated scenes from Dexter's childhood, marking the final scene with a smiley face. (Ep. 4) Rudy was trying to show Dexter that his upbringing was a sham.<br></p>
						<p>The ITK dove 200 feet to bring up one of Dexter's victims, Valerie Castillo. He marked the blood slide of her husband, Jorge Castillo, with a smiley face. The ITK was testing Dexter, to see if he could get himself out of trouble; to see if he would fight for his freedom. Dexter used that slide to frame Castillo for the murder of his wife, exonerating Dexter from suspicion. (Ep. 6)<br></p>
						<p>According to Dexter, the confessed suspect in custody for the ITK murders couldn't be the real ITK. Neil Perry's obsession with rogue taxidermy didn't fit the ITK's profile. Also, his prints didn't match the lozenge wrapper found at the Tony Tucci crime scene. (Ep. 7)<br></p>
						<p>Dexter posted an ad on Craigslist looking for his old friend the ITK. Unbeknownst to Dexter, Rudy replied. (Ep. 8)<br></p>
						<p>Detective Batista met a former prostitute with a prosthetic hand whose fingernails were painted like Sheri Taylor's fingertips, one of the ITK's previous victims.  The ITK left Sheri's severed hand in a block of ice in the recovered Ice Truck. Likewise, the ITK had painted the fingernails of the Barbie he left in Dexter's fridge. Batista went to interview Rudy about his knowledge of amputee fetishists.<br></p>
						<p>Batista was stabbed, and the amputee hooker was killed and dismembered, ITK style. Dexter found a cut on the back of Batista's head from where he head-butted his attacker, as well as a drop of blood on Batista's shirt collar that wasn't Batista's. Later, he noticed that Rudy had a fat lip. Suspicious, Dexter went through the dumpster behind Rudy's apartment building and stole a bloody cotton ball. He tested that blood against the sample on Batista's collar, and it matched! Rudy was the ITK!<br></p>
						<p>Dexter tore apart his apartment looking for clues. He found that Rudy had left him a new screensaver that played the song "Born Free," and a Barbie doll wearing a shirt that said "Home Sweet Home." Dexter realized that he was to go where he, as a killer, was born - the location of the massacre where he watched his mother's murder. Dexter went to the shipping container but all he found were bananas. Frustrated, Dexter went to Rudy's apartment where LaGuerta had already started investigating.<br></p>
						<p>Rudy, in anticipation of being caught, had vacated his apartment. But Dexter found a clue that Rudy had left just for him: a record player with the record 'Born Free,' and a Barbie Doll wearing a shirt that read 'Home Sweet Home.' Dexter realized Rudy was instructing him to go back to where he was born - literally. His childhood home. It was there that he had his confrontation with Brian/Rudy, and learned that Brian/Rudy was his biological brother.<br></p>
						<p>Brian/Rudy escaped from Dexter's childhood home after their confrontation, but Dexter knew he'd return and try to kill Debra again. He set a trap for Brian/Rudy, using the prosthetic copies of Debra's limbs Rudy had made (Ep. 8) as a Debra decoy. When Brian/Rudy went to kill the decoy, Dexter ambushed him with a garrote.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>PLACE OF DEATH:</h3>
						<p>Brian/Rudy's very own refrigerated kill room<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Unlike his usual M.O., Dexter sliced Brian/Rudy's throat with a silver dinner knife. He then hung Brian/Rudy upside down in the gravity boots that Brian/Rudy used to drain the blood of his ITK victims. Dexter not only varied the method of killing, but the ritual as well. First, he offered Rudy a tranquilizer to make the experience less painful and traumatic. Additionally, Dexter didn't take a blood slide from Brian/Rudy. He wasn't a trophy kill, like the others. Rather, Dexter put Rudy down, like a dog.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>None. Dexter left the body for the police to find, knowing it would appear that Brian/Rudy had staged a dramatic suicide.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=127821">S1.EP12 // "Born Free"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-moser-1.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-moser-2.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-moser-3.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-moser-4.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-moser-5.jpg" />
				</images>
				<audio src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/mp3/112_voiceover.mp3" />
				<video titleId="1159707963001" />
			</victim>
			<victim name="Mike Donovan" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/donovan.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/donovanColor.png"  primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Mike Donovan<br>
						1964 - 2006
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[I couldn't help myself.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"I couldn't help myself."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO MIKE WAS:</h3>
						<p>Church Choir Master, Husband, Child Rapist, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Per Harry's code, Dexter's killing must serve a purpose. He channels his urge to kill into something productive: he takes out people who deserve it.  Mike Donovan raped and murdered children, which Dexter proved when he dug up their bodies under Mike's house.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>MIKE'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Corey Balanti (12), Tyler Kale (14), Joe Bigalow (13)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter waited for Donovan after a choir performance in Donovan's Ford Taurus. When Donovan entered the car, Dexter, wearing a mask, emerged from the backseat and choked Donovan with fishing line, ordering him to drive to a house on the outskirts of Miami. Using said fishing line, Dexter dragged Donovan into the basement of the house. There, Dexter forced Donovan to look at the bodies of the young boys he had brutally slain. Then Dexter used a syringe to sedate him.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter converted a room on the second floor of Donovan's house to his kill room, draping it with plastic sheeting.  He then secured Mike to a table in the center of the room with plastic wrap and duct tape.  As Mike screamed, Dexter decapitated him with a surgical saw.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter cut Mike's body into pieces with his trusty surgical saw, wrapped the pieces in Hefty bags, and dumped them in the ocean from the deck of his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=127809">S1.EP01 // "Dexter"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-Mike-Donovan.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="James Jaworski" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/jaworski.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/jaworskiColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						James Jaworski<br>
						1977 - 2006
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[I'm not sorry.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"I'm not sorry."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO JAMES WAS:</h3>
						<p>Hotel Valet, Amateur Filmmaker, Peeping Tom, Thief, Rapist, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Per Harry's code, Dexter's killing must serve a purpose. He channels his urge to kill into something productive: he takes out people who deserve it. James raped and killed women on the S & M porn website 'Scream Bitch, Scream' - the mother of all rape sites.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>JAMES'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Jane Saunders, mother of two small boys<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter trailed James to his place of employment, where he noticed a distinct red devil tattoo on James's right forearm. Later, Dexter broke into James's house and found evidence that James frequented 'Scream, Bitch, Scream.' On the website, Dexter found a snuff video in which a masked man raped and stabbed Jane Saunders to death. The masked man had a tattoo that matched James's. Dexter then followed James to a half-built condo complex where James stole copper wire to sell. Wearing a creepy shrink wrap mask, Dexter surprised James with a photo of Jane Saunders and then used his tranquilizer syringe to sedate him.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter converted a section of the condo's basement to his kill room, draping it with plastic sheeting.  He then secured James to a stack of sheet rock in the center of the room with shrink wrap and duct tape. After slicing James's cheek for a blood sample, Dexter hacked James to pieces with a meat cleaver.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter wrapped the pieces of James's body in Hefty bags and dumped them in the ocean from the deck of his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=127809">S1.EP01 // "Dexter"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-Jaworski.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Matthew Chambers" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/chambers.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/chambersColor.png"  primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Matthew Chambers<br>
						1971 - 2006
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[It was me... only it wasn't me. It was the booze... it takes me over. I'm sorry]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"It was me... only it wasn't me. It was the booze... it takes me over. I'm sorry"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO MATT WAS:</h3>
						<p>Unemployed Alcoholic, Drunk Driver, Hitter and Runner, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Per Harry's code, Dexter's killing must serve a purpose. He channels his urge to kill into something productive: he takes out people who deserve it. Matt repeatedly drove drunk, and used the pretense of AA recovery to get a lesser sentence. After fulfilling his decreased sentence, he would move from city to city, changing his name to avoid further prosecution. Matt was clearly not recovered. In each city, he repeated his bad behavior without remorse.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>MATT'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Alexander Pryce (18) and at least two or three others in different states<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter attended Matt's trial, watching him hide behind a mask of empathy and sympathy for his addiction and recovery. Matt used his AA sponsor to vouch for his false recovery. But after Matt was found not guilty, Dexter overheard him talking to his lawyer about having beat the system. Dexter trailed Matt to a sports bar where he found him drinking (clearly not recovered). He got some face time and learned that Matt moved from place to place. He also pocketed Matt' drinking glass.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter ran the fingerprints he pulled off Matt's glass. He found DUI and hit and run offenses in New Mexico and Massachusetts. Matt was a repeat offender who made no effort to change his ways.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter waited for Matt outside his favorite liquor store. He snuck up behind him, and sedated him with the syringe. Matt was easy to surprise - he was drunk.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter turned an abandoned liquor store into his kill room. He draped it with plastic sheeting, a laptop played footage of Alexander Pryce's last Christmas, and the walls were lined with news clippings of Matt's New Mexico and Massachusetts victims. He first stabbed Matt in the abdomen with a knife, then butchered him with a surgical power saw. <br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter wrapped the pieces of Matt's body in Hefty bags and dumped them in the ocean from the deck of his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=127810">S1.EP2 // "Crocodile"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-Matt-Chambers.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Mary the Nurse" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/nursemary.png"  polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/nursemaryColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Mary the Nurse<br>
						1946 - 1991
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[I helped them. I took away their pain.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"I helped them. I took away their pain."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO MARY WAS:</h3>
						<p>Nurse, Blonde, Angel of Death, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Per Harry's code, Dexter's killing must serve a purpose. He channels his urge to kill into something productive: he takes out people who deserve it. Mary was Dexter's first kill - the first time Dexter implemented Harry's Code. Mary was Harry's nurse while he was hospitalized for a heart attack. She administered his morphine and attempted to kill him by overdose. Harry realized what was happening and asked Dexter to 'stop her... before she [hurt] anyone else.' Harry gave Dexter permission to use the lessons he taught him.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>MARY'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Phoebe Burns (60), Jason Kheel (82), David Nammers (73)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter broke into Mary's house and ambushed her, sticking her with a syringe like the one she used on his father. (This is the origin of Dexter's syringe technique.) But Mary was strong. She took the needle out of her neck and wrestled Dexter to the ground. Finally Dexter sedated her with a punch to the face.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Because it was his first kill, Dexter went slightly overboard, covering not just the kill room but the entire apartment in painter's plastic. Mary woke up shrink wrapped to a kill table, naked, with gauze in her mouth. Dexter perused her scrapbook of obituaries, removed the gauze, and asked her about her victims. He then stabbed her in the chest with a skinning knife (a gift from Harry).<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter fed Mary's body to the alligators in the Everglades.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=127811">S1.EP03 // "The Popping Cherry"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-Nurse-Mary.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Jorge Castillo" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/castillo.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/castilloColor.png"  primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Jorge Castillo<br>
						1969 - 2006
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[It was an accident. They... tried to escape.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"It was an accident. They... tried to escape."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO JORGE WAS:</h3>
						<p>Salvage yard manager, Husband, Cuban, Refugee smuggler, Extortionist, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Jorge moonlighted as a 'coyote,' smuggling Cuban refugees into the U.S. by boat. He then extorted the families of the refugees for a surprise 'release fee.' If the families couldn't come up with the money, he'd kill the refugee in question. Then he'd dump the refugee in the ocean, making him (or her) appear to be one more Cuban who didn't quite make it to shore.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>JORGE'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Countless Cuban refugees, most recently Ernesto Rodriguez (31)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Rita's coworker Yelina confided in Rita that she was being extorted by a coyote. Rita enlisted Dexter's help. Dexter contacted his cop friend, Officer Gerard, to get a list of suspected coyotes. He matched their names and addresses against the location where Yelina was told to drop the money for her fiancé Ernesto's release. Jorge's address matched up. Dexter found Jorge at his place of employment - a salvage yard. He spoke to Jorge and learned that he was also a boat owner. Later, Dexter snuck onto the salvage yard alone and found the garage where Jorge locked up his refugee prisoners. But he couldn't find a kill room. He stalked Jorge at his house with a telephoto camera lens. He took pictures of a Reefshore Marina sticker on Jorge's car. Dexter went to the Marina to search Jorge's boat.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter found three dead bodies floating in the fish hold of Jorge's boat. He took pictures.<br></p>
						<p>At the salvage yard, Dexter led Jorge to a junked Airstream trailer using a trail of religious votive candles. Once Jorge was inside the trailer, Dexter attacked him, getting him in a stranglehold and sedating him with his trusty syringe.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Jorge's death was complicated by the arrival of his wife Valerie. Dexter realized that she was in on the scheme and decided to kill her too. Dexter shrink wrapped and duct taped Jorge and Valerie to separate tables inside the plastic-draped Airstream.  On the back wall were the pictures Dexter took of the floating bodies - a Cuban woman, a Cuban grandmother, and a little boy. Dexter hacked up Jorge with a power saw.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter wrapped the pieces of Jorge's body in Hefty bags and dumped them in the ocean from the deck of his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=127813">S1.EP05 // "Love American Style"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-Jorge-Castillo.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Valerie Castillo" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/vcastillo.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/vcastilloColor.png"  primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Valerie Castillo<br>
						1971 - 2006
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[We share the same dreams. That's it.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"We share the same dreams. That's it."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO VALERIE WAS:</h3>
						<p>Homemaker, Wife, Refugee smuggler's accomplice, Extortionist, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Valerie was the brains behind her husband Jorge's extortion and killing plot.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>VALERIE'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Countless Cuban refugees, most recently Ernesto Rodriguez (31)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>When Dexter initially stalked Jorge, he assumed Valerie was ignorant of her husband's antics. But after Dexter abducted and sedated Jorge, Valerie pulled up in her car. Dexter witnessed her mistreating a refugee. Dexter then realized that she was in on the scam.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter shrink wrapped and duct taped Valerie to a separate table beside her husband Jorge inside the plastic-draped Airstream. Dexter killed Valerie with a power saw.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>This was the first time Dexter deviated from his original plan - he didn't initially intend to kill Valerie. Therefore, he didn't allot enough time for the killing and chopping up of both victims. Dexter ran out of time and had to leave Valerie's body whole. He wrapped her body in a bag and loaded it, as well as the pieces of Jorge, into his car. Before bringing the bodies to his boat, Dexter anonymously released the imprisoned refugees. He then took both bodies to his boat, the Slice of Life, and dumped the bodies in ocean.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=127813">S1.EP05 // "Love American Style"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-Valerie-Castillo.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Alex Timmons" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/timmons.png"  polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/timmonsColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Alex Timmons<br>
						1964 - 1999
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Yes, I did it. Is that what you want to hear?]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Yes, I did it. Is that what you want to hear?"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO ALEX WAS:</h3>
						<p>Sniper, Divorcee, Former Marine, Dishonorable Dischargee, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Alex shot and killed random, innocent individuals, terrorizing Miami for a month.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>ALEX'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Jennifer Newman (17), Ted Ambers (53), Gary West (37), Berry Costella (41)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>While out stalking another victim, Dexter saw Alex poised and ready to shoot. Dexter couldn't go to the police because his own alibi was incriminating. So he took care of the problem himself.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter trailed Alex to his home, where he found ammo that matched the bullets found in the victims. Dexter then waited for Alex in the alley outside a video store at night and nabbed him, sedating him with the syringe.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter set up his kill room on the roof of an abandoned motel. He shrink wrapped and duct taped Alex to a table, then butchered him with a chainsaw.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter dumped the individually-wrapped pieces of Alex in the ocean from the deck of his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=127814">S1.EP06 // "Return to Sender"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-Timmons.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Gene Marshall" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/marshall.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/marshallColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Gene Marshall<br>
						1948 - 2002
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Have you ever watched someone burn alive?]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Have you ever watched someone burn alive?"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO GENE WAS:</h3>
						<p>Fire Inspector, Arsonist, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Gene was an arsonist who burned down an apartment complex while residents were inside.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>GENE'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Herb Watson (73), Jacob Williams (31), Harold Tress (44), Bob Mority (27), Kim Yancy (29), Vince Colbert (33), Craig Johnson (40)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter examined Marshall's report that deemed the apartment fire an accident and noticed some inconsistencies. He broke into Gene's apartment and found that he kept personal files on several arson cases - fires Gene apparently set himself. He also found various fire-starting devices.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter caught Gene revisiting the scene of the crime. He tailed him and then sedated him with his syringe.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Gene's kill room was in the burned out ruins of the building. Dexter sliced Gene to pieces with a surgical saw.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter dumped the Hefty-wrapped chunks of Gene in the ocean from the deck of his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=127814">S1.EP06 // "Return to Sender"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-Marshall.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Cindy Landon" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/landon.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/landonColor.png"  primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Cindy Landon<br>
						1968 - 2004
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[I'll f**k you if you let me go.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"I'll f**k you if you let me go."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO CINDY WAS:</h3>
						<p>Hand Model, Serial Bride, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Cindy was a black widow. She married older men for their money and then killed them in their sleep.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>CINDY'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Norman Gork (77), Gilbert Connor (87), Jerry Rames (82)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter trailed Cindy to a pharmacy, where he saw her making out with a young pharmacist. Dexter spotted the two together on several other occasions - clearly romantically involved. It was clear Cindy wasn't in love with her husband.<br></p>
						<p>Pharmaceuticals showed up in the post mordem tox screen of Cindy's latest dead husband. Dexter uncovered evidence that Cindy procured the drugs from her pharmacist boyfriend.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter nabbed Cindy after a tryst with her boyfriend as she was returning to her sleeping husband.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter set up a kill room for Cindy in the cafeteria of a condemned convalescent home. He decorated it with obituaries of her late husbands. Cindy was slaughtered with a power saw.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter dumped Cindy's parts in the ocean from the deck of his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=127811">S1.EP06 // "Return to Sender"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-Cindy-Landon.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Emmett Meridian" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/meridian.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/meridianColor.png"  primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Emmett Meridian<br>
						1960 - 2006
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>None known<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO EMMETT WAS:</h3>
						<p>Psychotherapist, Professor of Psychology, Sympathetic Ear, Effective Persuader, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Dr. Meridian got powerful female patients addicted to anti-depressants and then abruptly pulled them off, making them suicidal. He then used his ample skills of persuasion to convince the women to commit suicide.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DR. MERIDIAN'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Vanessa Gayle (35), Meghan Dowd (34), Carolyn Jillian (36)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter was working blood spatter on the apparent suicide of Vanessa Gayle. He recalled that she wasn't the first powerful woman to shoot herself in recent years and decided to do some digging. He discovered that all three suicidal women shared the same therapist: Dr. Emmett Meridian.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter researched Dr. Meridian at the university where he taught psychology. He then scheduled a therapy appointment with Dr. Meridian, just to feel him out. Dexter found Meridian to be an incredibly helpful therapist, but also suspicious. He checked Meridian's appointment book to see where he was at the time of Vanessa Gayle's death. He confirmed Dr. Meridian's alibi, and then scheduled another appointment for further investigation. He noticed a hidden camera in Dr. Meridian's office. Later, he broke into the office to examine the camera, and found that it was attached to Dr. Meridian's computer. On Dr. Meridian's computer, Dexter found digital video recordings of sessions with Vanessa Gayle, Meghan Dowd, and Carolyn Jillian. All three asked for renewals on their prescriptions, and all three were subtly encouraged to take their own lives.<br></p>
						<p>In the middle of his final session, Dexter admitted to Dr. Meridian that he was a serial killer. Dr. Meridian thought Dexter was kidding at first. When it dawned on him that Dexter was serious, he attempted to leave his office. Dexter nabbed him, got him into a police chokehold, and sedated him with his syringe.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter turned Dr. Meridian's office into a kill room and shrink wrapped him to his own desk.  He then ripped Dr. Meridian apart with a surgical saw.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter dumped Dr. Meridian's parts in the ocean from the deck of his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=127816">S1.EP08 // "Shrink Wrap"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/0-Meridian.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
		</season>
		<season>
			<victim name="Lila West" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/lilawest.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/lilawestColor.png" primary="true">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Lila West<br>
						1976 - 2007
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Don't do this.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Don't do this."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO LILA WAS:</h3>
						<p>Artist, British Citizen, Illegal Alien, Support Group Habitué, Sociopath, Compulsive Arsonist, Kidnapper, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Lila killed Sgt. Doakes and attempted to kill Dexter, Astor and Cody. She also confessed to Dexter that she killed her former boyfriend. However, she told Dexter he deserved it, so per Harry's code, this is not reason enough to kill Lila.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LILA'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>James Doakes, and she attempted to murder Dexter, Astor and Cody<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Lila was Dexter's sponsor in Narcotics Anonymous. She quickly recognized a fellow sociopath in Dexter. She seduced him, which led to his temporary breakup with Rita. Lila became obsessed with winning over Dexter at any cost. She tracked him down to Jimenez's cabin, where she found Sgt. Doakes imprisoned. Doakes told Lila that Dexter was in fact the Bay Harbor Butcher, and Lila killed him to protect Dexter by exploding the cabin with a propane tank.<br></p>
<p>Dexter pretended that he was in love with Lila. He told her that he was going to run away with her, when in actuality he was planning to kill her. Dexter went to Lila's loft with his bag of kill tools to do the job, but his plot was thwarted when Debra showed up. Lila made off with Dexter's kill tools.<br></p>
<p>Lila then kidnapped Astor and Cody and took them to her loft, knowing Dexter would come there to find them. When Dexter arrived, she locked all three of them in the loft and set it on fire. They barely escaped with their lives.<br></p>
<p>Dexter finally tracked Lila down in Paris. He sent her a 'Greetings from Miami' postcard with Sgt. Doakes' picture on it. Lila received the postcard at her Paris apartment. Just as she was reacting to it, Dexter sprang on her and injected her with a spinal epidural. She remained conscious, but she couldn't move or feel anything.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter laid Lila's inert body on the couch and stabbed her through the heart.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter zipped Lila's body in a garment bag. How he disposed of it is not known.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=130359">S2.EP12 // "Waiting to Exhale"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-lila-1.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-lila-2.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-lila-3.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-lila-4.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-lila-5.jpg" />
				</images>
				<audio src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/mp3/212_voiceover.mp3" />
				<video titleId="1159702616001" />
			</victim>
			<victim name="Chino Gonzalez" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/gonzalez.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/gonzalexColor.png"  primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Chino Gonzalez<br>
						1972 - 2007
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[You kill me, what do you leave behind?]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"You kill me, what do you leave behind?"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO CHINO WAS:</h3>
						<p>"Little Chino," Member of the 29th Street Kings Gang, Tattoo Canvas, Enforcer, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Little Chino killed witnesses who wanted to testify against the 29th St. Kings, creating a climate of terror and obstructing justice. He was linked to nine murders in the last five years.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LITTLE CHINO'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Rafael Arenas (18), a 29th St. Kings member who was planning to leave the gang. Also, Chino put a hit our on Raphael's mother, Eva Arenas, who was going to testify as a witness against Little Chino.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter was called to Raphael Arenas' murder scene. Little Chino was the prime suspect, but Eva Arenas, the only witness, was deemed not credible due to her history of drug use. She was later killed by one of Chino's cronies, a murder for which Dexter held Chino directly responsible.<br></p>
						<p>Knowing that each drop of blood on Chino's tattoo represented a kill, Dexter realized Chino would need another blood drop following Raphael Arenas' death. Dexter called the gang task force and found out where the 29th St. Kings got their tattoos. He went to the tattoo parlor and waited for Little Chino to arrive.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter put half a dozen wild chickens in the back of Little Chino's car to use as a distraction. When Chino got out of the car to investigate the strange noises coming from the chickens, Dexter ambushed him with his syringe.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter's first attempt to kill Chino was unsuccessful. Little Chino was able to use his considerable bulk to break free of the shrink wrap holding him down and escape. <br></p>
						<p>Dexter obtained a tranquilizer stick designed for use on large animals and trailed Chino to a house party. But this time Chino was ready for Dexter. Chino sent his gang associates after Dexter, who spent the night hiding in a storm drain. Dexter then decided to use Joey Nunez, the young gang-tagger who ratted out the 29th St. King's, as bait. He followed the kid to a construction site, knowing that Chino would be coming for Nunez, just as he did for previous witnesses.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter trapped Chino in a freight elevator, jammed the tranq stick into his neck, and then used a construction dolly to transport Chino to the trunk of his own car.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter turned an abandoned auto body shop where Chino and his gang stored drugs into a kill room. He used a hydraulic auto lift to put Chino's body on the killing table. After Chino awoke, Dexter stabbed him in the heart with a machete.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter hacked Little Chino's enormous corpse to bits, wrapped the pieces in plastic and dumped them in the Gulf Stream from the deck of his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=130349">S2.EP02 // "Waiting to Exhale"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-Gonzales.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Roger Hicks" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/hicks.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/hicksColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Roger Hicks<br>
						1961 - 2007
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[You're better off without that c***!]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"You're better off without that c***!"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO ROGER WAS:</h3>
						<p>Car Salesman, Wig Wearer, Woman Hater, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Roger abused his position as a car salesman to hunt and kill unassuming, single women. Dexter was planning to lay low, but when he realized Roger had his next victim lined up he decided to take Roger out. Also, Roger called Rita a 'c***'."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>ROGER'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Ann Cohen, Lynn Hall, and his next potential victim was Allison Sera<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter visited Roger's dealership to get DNA evidence illegally, which the police couldn't do. Dexter discovered that Roger was not only a compulsive liar but a damn good salesman - he managed to sell Dexter a minivan. He took a hair from Roger, only to realize that the hair was synthetic - no DNA at all. Dexter visited the dealership a second time under the guise of discussing an extended warranty and stole a cigarette to get DNA. While there, he met Roger's next potential victim, Allison Sera. Dexter discovered Roger's method from his conversation with Allison.  Roger would run credit checks on attractive women, find out their marital status and address, and then send them to another dealership to avoid suspicion. He then went to their homes, where they allowed him inside because he wasn't a stranger, and he murdered them in cold blood.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter discovered that Roger did credit checks on both Ann Cohen and Lynn Hall. Roger's DNA from the cigarette matched DNA left at Ann Cohen's crime scene.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter ambushed Roger in the dealership parking lot. He confronted Roger about his lies, and then wrapped a garrote around his neck and choked him out. Dexter then threw Roger in the back of his newly purchased minivan, making use of the ample cargo space.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter set up Roger's kill room in Ann Cohen's house. As soon as Roger insulted Rita, Dexter slammed a knife into his chest, killing him.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter carved Roger into pieces, put them in garbage bags and dumped them in the Gulf Stream.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=130350">S2.EP03 // "An Inconvenient Lie"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-Hicks.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Ken Olson" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/olson.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/olsonColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Ken Olson<br>
						1972 - 2007
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[So you're not going to kill me?]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"So you're not going to kill me?"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO KEN WAS:</h3>
						<p>Unemployment sufferer, Vigilante Wannabe, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Inspired by the vigilante principles of the 'Bay Harbor Butcher,' Ken killed a nameless drug dealer by running him over with his car, and then pushed a domestic abuser down the stairs. Unfortunately, those victims didn't 'deserve it' according to Harry and Dexter's Code - which meant Olson was worthy of Dexter's blade.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>KEN'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>A nameless drug dealer and wife abuser. He also attempted to kill John Henry, an armed robber who preyed on the elderly, including Ken's mother.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter was called to the scene of Henry's attempted murder. Detective Batista realized that Ken's mother had been a victim of Henry's, which gave Ken the motive to kill him. Dexter got Ken's address from the task force file and broke into his house to find evidence for a warrant. Ken came home and found Dexter there.<br></p>
						<p>Dexter had no choice but to pounce, getting Ken in a chokehold. Dexter only intended to scare Ken into ceasing his vigilante attempts, but Ken confessed to murder in an attempt to bond with Dexter. It didn't work. Rather, it gave Dexter reason to kill him.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter took Ken to the empty train car where Ken had attempted to kill John Henry. Dexter dealt a fatal blow to Ken's neck with a meat cleaver.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter chopped Ken up and put the pieces in garbage bags. But he left the bags in the train car for the police task force to find, as a deterrent to other would-be vigilantes who wanted to emulate the Bay Harbor Butcher.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=130353">S2.EP06 // "Dex, Lies and Videotape"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-Olson.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Santos Jimenez" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/jimenez.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/jimenezColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Santos Jimenez<br>
						1950 - 2007
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[I'll F**king kill you!]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"I'll F**king kill you!"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO SANTOS WAS:</h3>
						<p>Tavern Owner, Cabin Dweller, Drug Dealer, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>In this case, it was also personal - Santos killed Dexter's mother, Laura Moser, for being a confidential informant to the police - more specifically to Harry, Dexter's foster father. Harry was emotionally devastated by her death because he felt responsible. In effect, killing Santos was Dexter's way of fully realizing Harry's intention.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>SANTOS'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Laura Moser<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter was convinced to find and kill Santos by Lila West, Dexter's lover. Lila felt it would help Dexter balance the scales.<br></p>
<p>Dexter went to the records office to find out what happened to his mother's murderers. He discovered that one man was deceased, one was doing life without the possibility of parole, and one was still an open case: Santos Jimenez. Jimenez turned state's evidence and went into witness protection. Still, Dexter managed to find him living in Naples, running a tavern.<br></p> 
<p>Dexter went to visit Santos at his tavern. Initially Dexter didn't kill Santos, he beat him up. Dexter was 'on the wagon' at the time, taking a break from killing. Later, however, Santos attacked Dexter at a bowling alley. Dexter decided to 'fall off the wagon' and go after Santos, administering justice once and for all. He went to Santos's tavern, waited for him, and then followed him to a remote cabin in the everglades where Santos stored cocaine.<br></p>
<p>Outside the cabin, Dexter turned on the radio in Santos's truck to attract his attention. When Santos came out, Dexter snuck up on him and plunged a needle into his neck.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter converted Santos's cabin into the kill room and shrink wrapped Santos to a table. Dexter then donned a soldering mask and killed Santos with a chainsaw, to commemorate the way Santos killed his own mother in front of him so many years ago.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter dismembered Santos with his trusty chainsaw and dumped the pieces in the Gulf Stream.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=130355">S2.EP08 // "Morning Comes"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-Jiminez.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Jose Garza" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/garza.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/garzaColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Jose Garza<br>
						1980 - 2007
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Where's my snow, mother**ker?]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Where's my snow, mother**ker?"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO JOSE WAS:</h3>
						<p>Record Store Clerk, Drug Dealer, Armed Robber, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Jose murdered a drug dealer who sold him cocaine and never delivered. Dexter knew Jose was looking for Santos Jimenez, Dexter's most recent victim. Dexter realized that if Jose knew about Jimenez's cabin, he could stumble upon Sgt. Doakes, whom Dexter had imprisoned there. Once Dexter discovered that Jose was a murderer, he figured he could kill several birds with one stone - protect himself from discovery, take out a bad guy, and leave a body with Doakes, framing him for the Bay Harbor murders once and for all.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>JOSE'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Ben 'Spider' Koff (23)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Jose texted Jimenez's phone, looking for cocaine, and Dexter found the phone in Jimenez's cabin. Dexter found out that the texter's phone number belonged to Christopher Harlow, one of Jose's known aliases. Using Jimenez's phone, Dexter texted Jose to meet him at Jimenez's cabin. When Jose replied, 'what cabin,' Dexter knew he was no longer at risk of discovery. Later, when Jose located the cabin, Dexter decided it was time to take him out. He texted Jose to meet him at Jimenez's bar. There, Dexter snuck up on Jose and stuck him with a syringe.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter hung plastic sheeting between Jose's kill room and Sgt. Doakes so Doakes wouldn't have to watch the kill. He also didn't take a blood sample or wait for Jose to wake up. He stabbed Jose in the chest, killing him while he slept.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter cut Jose into pieces, wrapped the pieces in garbage bags as usual and left them in the cabin with Doakes. The body would provide hard evidence that Doakes was the Bay Harbor Butcher.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=130357">S2.EP10 // "There's Something About Harry"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-Garza.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Juan Rinez" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/rinez.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/rinezColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Juan Rinez<br>
						1964 - 1993
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[The bitches asked for it]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"The bitches asked for it"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO JUAN WAS:</h3>
						<p>Cuban, Pimp, Assaulter, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Juan beat one of his girls to death, blunt trauma to the back of the head. Harry had tracked Juan for years and Dexter killed him to earn Harry's approval.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>JUAN'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Julie Piotrowski (18)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter went to the crime scene with Harry, who told him Juan was responsible for the girl's death. The day Juan was released from prison due to a faulty warrant, Dexter found him at home and attacked him, using chloroform to anesthetize him.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter created a kill room in an abandoned garage. He stabbed Juan to death.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter sliced Juan's body into pieces then fed the pieces to the alligators in the Everglades.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=130357">S2.EP10 // "There's Something About Harry"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-Garza.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Teo Famosa" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/famosa.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/famosaColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Teo Famosa<br>
						1975 - 2007
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Esteban!]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Esteban!"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO TEO WAS:</h3>
						<p>Drug Runner, Illegal Alien, Kidnapper<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Self-defense<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>TEO'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>None known<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Teo and his brother Esteban came across Sgt. Doakes as he was escaping from Jimenez's cabin where Dexter had imprisoned him. Dexter returned to the cabin and found the Famosa brothers stealing Jimenez's cocaine and forcing Doakes to be their mule. Dexter and Doakes teamed up to kill the brothers.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Sgt. Doakes threw the cocaine bricks he was carrying in Teo's face to distract him, and Dexter used Esteban's gun to shoot Teo in the head.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter fed Teo's body to the alligators in the Everglades.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=130358">S2.EP11 // "Left Turn Ahead"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-t-famosa.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Esteban Famosa" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/efamosa.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/efamosaColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Esteban Famosa<br>
						1982 - 2007
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Mas coca.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Mas coca."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO ESTEBAN WAS:</h3>
						<p>Drug Runner, Illegal Alien, Kidnapper<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Self-defense<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>ESTEBAN'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>None known<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Esteban and his brother Teo came across Sgt. Doakes as he was escaping from Jimenez's cabin where Dexter had imprisoned him. Dexter returned to the cabin and found the Famosa brothers stealing Jimenez's cocaine and forcing Doakes to be their mule. Dexter and Doakes teamed up to kill the brothers.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter snapped Esteban's neck with his bare hands.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter fed Esteban's body to the alligators in the Everglades.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=130358">S2.EP11 // "Left Turn Ahead"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/1-E-Famosa.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
		</season>
		<season>
			<victim name="Miguel Prado" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/prado.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/pradoColor.png" primary="true">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Miguel Prado<br>
						1961 - 2008
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[You little f**k, you think I'm done with you? You think this ends here, it doesn't.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"You little f**k, you think I'm done with you? You think this ends here, it doesn't."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO MIGUEL WAS:</h3>
						<p>Assistant District Attorney, Brother, Husband, Lover, Friend, Jury Tamperer, Witness Intimidator, Avenger, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Miguel killed an innocent person, Ellen Wolf, and it was clear he had no remorse. Moreover, Lt. LaGuerta was next on Miguel's list. Dexter had to put Miguel down to prevent him from killing more people for selfish purposes. He also feared that Miguel would reveal his secret.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>MIGUEL'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Billy Fleeter (40), Ellen Wolf (38)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter found Ellen Wolf's body in the cemetery. Because Dexter told Miguel that's where he disposed of bodies, he knew that it had to be Miguel who put Ellen in the empty grave. Dexter also found Ellen's wedding band in Miguel's cigar humidor, further proving his guilt in her murder. In Miguel's hotel room, Dexter found a life-vest, indicating that Miguel had been back to the hardware store to purchase killing supplies. He also found an email notifying Miguel that LaGuerta was running hair and fibers she found in his car against Ellen Wolf's samples, which confirmed to Miguel that LaGuerta was a threat to him. Finally, Dexter saw Miguel getting his alcoholic brother Ramon drunk so he could use him as an alibi for the time of LaGuerta's murder.<br></p> 
<p>Usually when Dexter's victims disappeared, nobody noticed or cared. But Miguel was a high profile kill. When he disappeared there would be a massive investigation. Dexter couldn't disappear Miguel's body. He would need a particularly well-thought-out plan, an airtight alibi, and someone on whom he could pin Miguel's murder.<br></p>
<p>Dexter planned to pin Miguel's murder on The Skinner - George King. The Skinner had motive. He was looking for Freebo, and Miguel was looking for the man who killed Oscar, ostensibly Freebo. It would make sense that King would go after Miguel to get information on Freebo.<br></p>
<p>At Dexter's bachelor party, he realized that Miguel was using his brother Ramon for security. That was a complication Dexter would have to deal with. He followed Miguel to the hotel where he was staying post-argument with his wife Sylvia (she caught him with Lt. LaGuerta). Since Miguel was no longer living at home, he had an entirely new routine, one with which Dexter would have to become familiar.<br></p>
<p>Dexter tracked Miguel to LaGuerta's house, where he watched Miguel discover that LaGuerta suspected him in Ellen Wolf's murder. Dexter immediately knew this put LaGuerta in Miguel's crosshairs, but needed to be sure. He snuck into Miguel's hotel room, where he found evidence that Miguel was planning to take out LaGuerta that very night.<br></p>
<p>Dexter knew Miguel would be going to LaGuerta's to abduct her, so he called LaGuerta and asked her to meet him at a cafe, insuring her safety. He then went to LaGuerta's and waited for Miguel outside her front door. When Miguel realized LaGuerta wasn't there, he left... and Dexter promptly stuck him with his trusty syringe.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter set up the kill room in Ellen Wolf's office, ironically the same place Miguel had intended to kill LaGuerta. Dexter copied the Skinner's MO, strangling Miguel and then removing a small patch of skin post mortem.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter dumped Miguel's body in a park so the Skinner would be blamed for his murder.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=133006">S3.EP11 // "I Had a Dream"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/2-prado-1.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/2-prado-2.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/2-prado-3.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/2-prado-4.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/2-prado-5.jpg" />
				</images>
				<audio src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/mp3/312_voiceover.mp3" />
				<video titleId="1178540177001" />
			</victim>
			<victim name="Clemson Galt" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/galt.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/galtColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Clemson Galt<br>
						1967 - 2008
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[No, you've got me mixed up with somebody else.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"No, you've got me mixed up with somebody else."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO CLEMSON WAS:</h3>
						<p>Former Construction Worker, Prisoner, Armed Robber, White Supremacist, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Clemson killed Jenna Kendrick for getting pregnant. But he skated because his Aryan associates got witnesses to recant, or made them disappear. Clemson was serving 20 years in a maximum security prison for armed robbery, but he was still running things from the inside - the wife and three children of an Aryan defector also turned up dead. Dexter knew prison wasn't enough to protect people from Clemson. Clemson had to die.<br></p>
<p>Dexter was also testing Miguel to see how 'like-minded' they really were. As a Supermax prisoner, Clemson was impossible to get to without Miguel's help. Dexter figured if Miguel was willing to put himself on the line to get Clemson out of prison to help Dexter kill him, then Miguel truly was his friend. Dexter assumed Miguel would never go through with it. He assumed wrong.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>CLEMSON'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Jenna Kendrick (25), and many others<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Clemson's had been one of the first blood spatter cases Dexter ever worked. It had haunted him ever since. Miguel subpoenaed Clemson as an expert witness in a money laundering case. The plan was to transport Clemson to testify, thereby bringing him within Dexter and Miguel's reach. Miguel walked Dexter through the courthouse, showing him the layout so they could expertly make the grab. Statistically, most escapes happen in courthouses, so Clemson's disappearance could plausibly be mistaken as an escape, making it easy for Dexter and Miguel to cover their tracks.<br></p>
<p>On the day Clemson was supposed to testify, Miguel met with him and slipped him a handcuff key, suggesting that Clemson escape into the parking garage, where one of his 'Nazi pals' would be waiting for him. But in actuality, Dexter was waiting for him - posing as a member of the Aryan brotherhood. Dexter didn't plan to use the M-99 until he got Clemson to the car.
A complication arose when a deputy went into the holding cell to put a wristband on Clemson and discovered that he had escaped. The deputy sounded the alarm, and Dexter was forced to stick Clemson with the M-99 so he wouldn't turn himself in. Dexter thought Miguel would sell him out to save his own ass, but instead Miguel pulled a car around and helped Dexter escape with Clemson.
<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter took Clemson to an empty house for sale - the house where Clemson killed Jenna Kendrick. Dexter told Miguel to meet him elsewhere, pulling a bait and switch. Although Miguel proved his loyalty to Dexter, Dexter still wanted the ritual of the kill to be his, and his alone. Inside the pre-readied kill room, Dexter plunged a knife into Clemson's chest.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter cut Clemson's body up into pieces, put them into garbage bags and dumped them into the Gulf Stream. But Dexter told Miguel he took Clemson straight to the cemetery and dumped him in an empty grave. He didn't want to share that part of his ritual yet... if ever.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=133001">S3.EP06 // "Si Se Puede"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/2-Galt.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>	
			<victim name="Jorge Orozco" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/king.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/kingColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Jorge Orozco (aka George Washington King)<br>
						1954 - 2008
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Let's hope you're this talkative once I get my tools.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Let's hope you're this talkative once I get my tools."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO JORGE'S WAS:</h3>
						<p>Landscaper, Nicaraguan Resistance Leader, Criminal Mastermind, Kidnapper, Torturer, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>To save his own life, get to his wedding, and live to see the birth of his child. Plus Jorge skinned and killed several victims in his search for Freebo.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>JORGE'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Teegan Campbell, Javier Garza, Wendell Owens, Anton Briggs (survived) and, according to the police, Miguel Prado (Dexter framed Jorge for Prado's murder.)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter didn't track Jorge, Jorge tracked Dexter. Jorge was looking for Freebo, who owed him a lot of money. In his search, Jorge tortured and killed anyone he believed had information on Freebo's whereabouts. Miguel Prado told Jorge that Dexter knew where Freebo, and his money, could be located.<br></p>
<p>Miami Metro's investigation led to Jorge as the Skinner. Debra figured out that the Skinner was using the trees as cover for surveillance, so she brought in various landscapers and tree-trimmers for questioning. One of them, Mario Astorga, revealed that Jorge was someone to be feared. This information, combined with the Nicaraguan Embassy's records of Jorge's past as 'El Fierro,' The Blade, indicated that Jorge was definitely the Skinner.<br></p>
<p>Dexter's apartment was broken into, and he was later followed by car. Dexter assumed the person to blame was Ramon Prado, Miguel's brother. But a conversation with Ramon put those suspicions to rest. Dexter had no idea Jorge was onto him.<br></p> 
<p>Jorge abducted Dexter outside a tailor shop, smashing him in the head with a maglite. Jorge took Dexter to an old, abandoned cigar factory and tied him to a table. When Jorge left briefly to get his torture tools, Dexter was able to tilt the table over and crush his own hand, thereby enabling him to slide it through the rope binding his wrists.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter and Jorge fought brutally. Dexter was able to snap Jorge's neck and kill him just as the police were entering the factory.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Thinking fast, Dexter hurled Jorge's body out the window of the factory. It landed right in front of an arriving police car, which ran over it. The impact was blamed for Jorge's broken neck.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=133007">S3.EP12 // "Do You Take Dexter Morgan?"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/2-King.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Ethan Turner" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/turner.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/turnerColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Ethan Turner<br>
						1973 - 2008
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Hey.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>Hey.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO ETHAN WAS:</h3>
						<p>Boy Toy, Con Man, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Ethan married a rich older woman who 'overdosed' on pills, Ethan's pills. Translation: Ethan killed her for her money. He had already negotiated a very favorable pre-nuptial agreement. After Ethan's first wife was gone, he met another wealthy woman, married her, and subsequently threw her overboard on a cruise ship. Again, a pre-nuptial agreement left him quite well taken care of.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>ETHAN'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Two ex-wives<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>After hearing about Ethan from Miguel Prado, Dexter did some research on his own to make sure Ethan fit his Code. He then tracked Ethan to a sporting goods store and found him in excellent spirits for a man who recently lost his wife. In fact, Ethan was even using his late wife's credit card to buy scuba gear for a cruise whose first port was Bimini. Convinced of Ethan's guilt, Dexter took 'Slice of Life' to Bimini to find him. Ethan was already hitting on other women, ready to find his next mark. Dexter followed him onto the cruise ship./p><br>
<p>Dexter snuck into Ethan's suite on the ship. He waited until Ethan was getting out of the shower, then stuck him with the tranquilizer, M-99.
<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter quickly set up Ethan's suite as the kill room while Ethan was tranquilized. Dexter brought the necessary items - plastic wrap, tarps, his tools, etc. - inside a golf bag so as not to attract suspicion. He didn't use a kill table, instead he wrapped Ethan in plastic and knelt on him to hold him in place.  Dexter stabbed Ethan in the heart and listened to it as it stopped beating.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter cut up the body and put it in garbage bags. He threw the bags out the port hole in the room - the ship was conveniently right over the Gulf Stream.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=133000">S3.EP05 // "Turning Biminese"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/2-Turner.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Nathan Marten" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/marten.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/martenColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Nathan Marten<br>
						1974 - 2008
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>None<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO NATHAN WAS:</h3>
						<p>Amateur Photographer, Convicted Felon, Former Prisoner, Child Molester<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>While Marten may not have actually committed murder, he still destroyed lives by sexually assaulting children. And when Marten set his eyes on Astor and Cody, Dexter made an exception to his usual rule of only killing other killers in the interest of the children's safety.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>NATHAN'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Countless children<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter caught Marten talking to Astor in the grocery store. Astor said he wanted to know where the Cheerios were, but Dexter's killer instincts could see Marten for what he really was: a monster. Dexter took down Marten's license plate number in the parking lot and used it to get a name from the DMV records. Dexter then ran the name Nathan Marten through the sexual predators database and got a match. Marten did four years at South Bay Correctional Facility for sexual assault.<br></p>
<p>After spotting Marten again at the beach taking pictures of Astor and Cody, Dexter followed him to a children's play area at a restaurant. Dexter warned Marten to stay away from his kids.<br></p>
<p>Dexter then went to Marten's residence, where he decided Marten didn't fit his Code. But still, he returned to Marten's one more time and caught him looking at pictures of Astor and Cody. At that moment, Dexter realized Marten fit another kind of code - Dexter's code to protect his children.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter garroted Marten while he looked at pictures of Astor and Cody. He choked him to death on the spot.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter dragged Nathan's body out of his house, grabbing milk for his kids' cereal from Nathan's fridge as he left. He dumped Nathan's body in the Gulf Stream.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=132998">S3.EP03 // "The Lion Sleeps Tonight"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/2-Marten.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Freebo" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/bowman.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/bowmanColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Fred Bowman (aka 'Freebo')<br>
						1985 - 2008
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[No, not Teegan. I was getting high with Sheri, or Terri, or... She's a hell of a f--]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"No, not Teegan. I was getting high with Sheri, or Terri, or... She's a hell of a f--"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO FREEBO WAS:</h3>
						<p>Drug Dealer, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Freebo killed two college girls and skated on a Police screw up. Plus Dexter had an additional motive - he needed to kill Freebo before the police got to him. Freebo could have ID'd Dexter in Oscar Prado's murder.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>FREEBO'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Two college girls, and possibly his girlfriend, Teegan Campbell (21)<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Miami Metro investigated the murder of the two college girls. When Freebo got off on a technicality, he dropped off the police radar. But not Dexter's. Dexter went to Freebo's apartment under the guise of buying drugs. But when Dexter returned to abduct Freebo, he was caught off guard by the presence of Oscar Prado. While Dexter was busy killing Oscar, Freebo escaped.<br></p>
<p>After dealing with Oscar Prado's murder, Dexter turned his attention back to finding Freebo. Dexter went to Teegan's sorority house to look through her things, trying to find evidence of where Freebo might be, but two drunk girls told Dexter Teegan moved off campus. Dexter went to Teegan's apartment and was surprised to find Freebo himself there. He was using her apartment to hide out. Dexter decided to return for him later, when he had his kill tools with him.<br></p>
<p>Dexter snuck up on Freebo while he was eating cereal out of the box, garroted him, and dragged him from the apartment to the detached garage, where Dexter had prepared the kill room.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter shrink wrapped Freebo to a ladder in the kill room. Using Oscar Prado's knife, he stabbed Freebo in the neck, severing his carotid artery.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter hacked Freebo's body into pieces, wrapped them in garbage bags and dumped them in the Gulf Stream. But not before he was caught by Miguel Prado, Oscar's brother, who was waiting outside the garage to kill Freebo himself. Dexter had to confess to the crime, and Miguel Prado thanked him.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=132995">S3.EP02 // "Finding Freebo"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/2-Bowman_Freebo.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Oscar Prado" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/oprado.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/opradoColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Oscar Prado<br>
						1978 - 2008
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Who are you?]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Who are you?"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO OSCAR WAS:</h3>
						<p>Teacher, Basketball Coach, Cuban-American, Attacker<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Self-defense.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>OSCAR'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>None<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter had intended to kill Fred Bowman, AKA Freebo. But when he arrived Oscar and Freebo were fighting. Oscar came at Dexter with a knife.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter and Oscar struggled, and Dexter wrestled Oscar's knife from him and stabbed him to death with it. It was kill or be killed./p><br>
<p>This is the first time Dexter killed impulsively. And if he didn't know it was wrong, it might have felt... good.
<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter didn't dispose of the body. He left it at the scene, knowing Freebo would be blamed for the murder... with a little help from Miami Metro's own blood spatter expert: Dexter.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=132994">S3.EP01 // "Our Father"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/2-O-Prado.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>					
		</season>
		<season>
			<victim name="The Trinity Killer" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/arthur-mitchell.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/arthur-mitchellColor.png" primary="true">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Arthur Mitchell "The Trinity Killer"<br>
						1949 - 2009
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[It's already over. Could you? Thank you.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"It's already over. Could you? Thank you."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO ARTHUR WAS:</h3>
						<p>Teacher, Volunteer, Church Elder, Family Man, Trauma Victim, Enigma, Abuser, Sociopath, Possible Schizophrenic, Kidnapper, Torturer, Serial Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Arthur was the infamous Trinity Killer, implicated in the deaths of over one hundred innocent people<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>ARTHUR'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Rita Morgan, Dexter's wife, and many, many others<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter immediately became intrigued when FBI agent Lundy announced that a series of three recent deaths in Miami were being attributed to the Trinity Killer, the most prolific serial killer in American history. The Trinity Killer began his spree in Miami thirty years previously before moving on to other cities around the country, and it appeared that he had come back to kill again.<br></p>
<p>Dexter quickly identified Arthur as the Trinity Killer, but was surprised to learn that he was also a devoted family man, a devout churchgoer and a prominent philanthropist. Rather than killing him right away, Dexter decided to befriend Arthur to learn how he was able to live such a successful, balanced life and still satisfy his need to kill. Taking on the alias Kyle Butler, Dexter got close to Arthur through his Christian homebuilding organization.<br></p>
<p>Dexter concocted a plan to accompany Arthur on a road trip to Tampa. His intention was to kill Arthur along the way. But Arthur managed to extract a confession from 'Kyle' that he had killed someone. Arthur immediately saw this as a sign of kinship. He admitted to 'Kyle' that he had caused his sister's accidental death in the shower when they were young, which led to his mother's eventual suicide and his father's alcoholism and beating death. Dexter theorized that these incidents had triggered Arthur's dark side, as they closely mirrored the methods he used to kill his own victims.<br></p>
<p>Dexter snuck into Arthur's Tampa hotel room to kill him, but Arthur was gone. Dexter tracked him down on a rooftop, just as Arthur was about to jump to his death. Dexter stopped him - he wanted to be the cause of Arthur's death. This had the unintended consequence of bonding Arthur to 'Kyle' more than ever.<br></p>
<p>As Dexter got to know Arthur better, he realized that he wasn't the loving family man he appeared to be. Arthur's wife and children were terrified of him and resented him. He was extremely domineering and controlling, and even verbally and physically abusive.<br></p>
<p>Arthur also tried to resume his killing ways. He kidnapped a young boy with the intention of burying him alive in cement, as he had done with countless boys before him. Dexter stepped in and saved the boy. This made Arthur suspicious of Dexter. Also, the police were closing in on Arthur. He was brought in to the station for questioning and learned Dexter's true identity. Dexter knew it was time to act.<br></p>
<p>Arthur was planning a quick getaway in his vintage convertible sports car. As Arthur was driving out of town, Dexter ambushed him, and after a brief scuffle, stuck Arthur with a syringe, knocking him out.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter created a kill room for Arthur in the basement of the house where Arthur tried to kill his latest victim. The walls of the kill room were hung with dozens of photographs - all victims of the Trinity Killer. Dexter used the claw end of a hammer to bash Arthur's brains in, the same weapon Arthur used in many of his kills.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter disposed of Arthur's body in his usual manner, tossing plastic wrapped body parts into the Gulf Stream from his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE AFTERMATH:</h3>
						<p>Dexter arrived home, thinking Rita had already left for their vacation to the Keys. He found her dead in the bathtub, with his son Harrison crying at her side in a pool of blood. Arthur's final victim was Dexter's wife, and Dexter's son had witnessed the killing in the same way that Dexter had witnessed his mother's murder when he was a toddler.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135078">S4.EP12 // "The Getaway"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/3-arthur-1.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/3-arthur-2.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/3-arthur-3.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/3-arthur-4.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/3-arthur-5.jpg" />
				</images>
				<audio src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/mp3/412_voiceover.mp3" />
				<video titleId="1159707962001" />
			</victim>
			<victim name="Benito 'Benny' Gomez" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/gomez.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/gomezColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Benito "Benny" Gomez<br>
						1972 - 2009
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[I know you.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"I know you."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO BENNY WAS:</h3>
						<p>Retired Boxer, Lucky Break Receiver, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Benny bludgeoned a man to death in front of his son, and beat his girlfriend to death.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>BENNY'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>His girlfriend, a father of two<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Benny was being prosecuted for murder, but he got off on a technicality.  Namely, Dexter brought the wrong evidence to the trial. He was sleep deprived because of his new infant son.<br></p>
<p>Wracked with guilt over his mistake, Dexter used Quinn's case records to locate Benny at home in his trailer. Dexter quickly stuck Benny with a syringe, knocking him out.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter set up his kill room in a boxing ring at an abandoned boxing facility. Just as he was about to kill Benny, his phone rang. Rita told Dexter that Harrison had an ear infection, and she needed him to pick up a prescription immediately. Dexter was forced to cut his ritual short and kill Benny quickly.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Lacking time for a proper disposal, Dexter was forced to stuff Benny's body inside an old punching bag and suspend it above the ring. The problem was, he was so exhausted he got in an accident on his way home and forgot what he did with it. He eventually remembered the boxing ring, and located the body by the blood dripping down from the punching bag. He then unloaded Benny's remains in the usual way.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135067">S4.EP01 // "Living the Dream"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/3-gomez.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Zoey Kruger" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/kruger.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/krugerColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Zoey Kruger<br>
						1975 - 2009
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[You will choose your life over theirs.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"You will choose your life over theirs."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO ZOEY WAS:</h3>
						<p>Police Officer, Widow, Former Mother, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Zoey faked a home invasion so that she could kill her husband and daughter. She also framed a drug dealer, Darius Rey, who later died under fishy circumstances.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>ZOEY'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Her husband, her daughter. Suspected in the death of Darius Rey<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter noticed some discrepancies in the blood spatter report from the shootings in Zoey's home in which her husband and daughter were killed. When Zoey decided to sell her home, Dexter attended the open house to investigate further. While Zoey was busy with a perspective buyer, Dexter discovered a scrap of a latex glove in her garbage disposal. A lab analysis of the scrap revealed blood and gunpowder residue, confirming that Zoe used her own gun to kill her family.<br></p>
<p>Zoe caught on to Dexter's investigation and threatened him. Dexter intentionally agitated her, knowing she would come to his home based on her threats. She did indeed try to stage another 'home invasion' at Dexter's house, but he was waiting for her and subdued her.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter set up Zoey's kill room in her daughter's former bedroom.  He put pictures of her family in a baby mobile and dangled it over the bed where Zoey was constrained with plastic wrap. Zoey admitted that she felt suffocated by her family and had to kill them to be free.  Dexter identified with her feelings, but ultimately decided he would choose to be caught rather than give up his family. He plunged a knife into Zoey's chest, killing her.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter packed Zoey's suitcases and purchased her a one-way ticket to the Phillipines from her home, so her disappearance would not be suspicious. He then chopped her corpse into pieces and dumped them into the Gulf Stream from his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135070">S4.EP04 // "Dex Takes a Holiday"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/3-Kruger.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Jonathan Farrow" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/farrow.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/farrowColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Jonathan Farrow<br>
						1976 - 2009
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Because of my pictures, those women will live on forever!]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Because of my pictures, those women will live on forever!"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO JONATHAN WAS:</h3>
						<p>Photographer, Sadist, Accused Rapist, A**hole, but not a Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Dexter suspected Jonathan of killing at least three of the models that he photographed<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>JONATHAN'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>None<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Jonathan first appeared on Dexter's radar when the severed arm of one of his models, Estrella Caraza, was found inside an alligator. Dexter went to Jonathan's studio and discovered blood drops and a chipped fingernail that turned out to be Caraza's. This convinced him of Jonathan's guilt.<br></p>
<p>Dexter abducted Farrow from his home and garroted him with a wire to render him unconscious.
<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter converted Jonathan's photography studio to a kill room. He shrink wrapped Jonathan to a lighted table and projected images of his victims on the wall. Jonathan admitted that he beat the women he photographed for 'artistic' purposes, but he swore he never killed anyone. Dexter didn't believe him. Dexter chopped Jonathan's head off with a meat cleaver.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter dismembered Jonathan with his cleaver and dumped the chunks into the Gulf Stream from his boat, Slice of Life.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135073">S4.EP07 // "Slack Tide"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/3-Farrow.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Stan Beaudry" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/beaudry.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/beaudryColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Stan Beaudry<br>
						1950 - 2009
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[You'll be sorry that you ever crossed me!]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"You'll be sorry that you ever crossed me!"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO STAN WAS:</h3>
						<p>Truck Driver, Suspect, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Stan beat a hooker to death with a crowbar, but his case was dismissed on a technicality involving the evidence chain of command. Dexter needed to frame another suspect in the Trinity Killer case to buy himself more time to catch Arthur Mitchell, and Stan was his unlucky choice.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>STAN'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>An unnamed prostitute<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter found Stan's driving itinerary in Stan's residence. He tracked Stan down to a truck stop outside Jacksonville, Florida via CB radio.<br></p>
<p>Dexter needed to perform this kill quickly and get back to Miami, so while Stan was inside the restaurant, Dexter broke into his truck and set up a makeshift kill room in the back. As soon as Stan returned, Dexter garroted him with a wire.
<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter killed Stan quickly, but Stan gave him a good fight, struggling mightily until the end.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Before disposing of Stan's remains, Dexter planted Arthur Mitchell's DNA in the truck, implicating him in the crime.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/3-Beaudry.jpg" />
				</images>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135077">S4.EP11 // "Hello, Dexter Morgan"</a>
				</episode>
			</victim>
		</season>
		<season>
			<victim name="Jordan Chase" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/jordanchase.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/jordanchaseColor.png" primary="true">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Jordan Chase (ne Eugene Greer)<br>
						1974 - 2010
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[I watched you so carefully the last time you were here. You used to just cower and cry.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"I watched you so carefully the last time you were here. You used to just cower and cry."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO JORDAN WAS:</h3>
						<p>Charismatic Self-Help Guru, Former Fat Kid, Expert Persuader, Mastermind, Kidnapper, Videographer, Accomplice to Torture and Rape, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Jordan Chase was the mastermind behind a serial killing gang that kidnapped, raped and tortured twelve women before shoving their bodies in barrels and dumping them in a swamp. Although Jordan never actually committed any of the crimes, he convinced his childhood friends Cole Harmon, Boyd Fowler and Dan Mendell to do them while he stood by and filmed the whole thing.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>JORDAN'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Jordan arranged for the murder of twelve pretty young women, all blond, and actually murdered Emily Birch.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Jordan wasn't initially a suspect in the Barrel Girls case. Dexter assumed that his chief of security, Cole Harmon, was the ringleader. But while Dexter was attending one of Jordan's self-help seminars to trap Harmon, Jordan told Dexter, 'Tick, tick, tick. That's the sound of your life running out.' Dexter recognized these as the words Lumen had heard from the mastermind of her group of attackers. He and Lumen now knew that Jordan Chase was their main target.<br></p>
<p>Miami Metro was closing in on Jordan as well. In addition, Debra had theorized that there was a vigilante on the loose - that one of the Barrel Girls had escaped and was systematically killing her former attackers.<br></p>
<p>Lumen received a phone call from Emily Birch, Chase's first rape victim who also managed to survive. Emily said that Jordan knew that she and Lumen were working together, and she was going to go to the police for protection. Lumen begged Emily not to go to the police, that she and Dexter would come to protect her instead. But it was a trap. Emily was being controlled by Jordan, who had forced her to make the call.<br></p>
<p>Convinced that Emily was in grave danger, Lumen went to her house without Dexter, who was being detained by Stan Liddy at the time. Jordan was waiting for Lumen. When Lumen tried to escape, Jordan threatened to kill her with a fireplace poker. Emily tried to stop him, and Jordan killed Emily with the poker instead.<br></p>
<p>Jordan abducted Lumen, threw her in the trunk of his car and took her to the abandoned children's camp where he and his gang members had carried out their crimes. But he was spotted by a witness, who tipped off the police.<br></p>
<p>Dexter grabbed his trusty kill tools and tracked Jordan and Lumen to the camp. Jordan was waiting for him when he got there. He managed to catch Dexter, tie him up and take him to the basement of a cabin, where he also had Lumen tied up. Jordan opened Dexter's beautiful set of kill tools and prepared to kill both Dexter and Lumen, when he noticed that one of the knives was missing. At that moment, the shackled Dexter managed to plunge the missing knife into Jordan's foot. As Jordan screamed in agony, Dexter got him in a choke hold and subdued him.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter and Lumen set up a kill room in the cabin's basement and secured Jordan to a table with belts. When Jordan awoke from his M-99 injection, they were waiting. But it was Lumen who ultimately killed Jordan, plunging the knife into Jordan's chest with defiant satisfaction.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>As Dexter and Lumen were cleaning up the kill room, Debra arrived. She saw figures moving behind the plastic kill room curtain but couldn't see who they were. Debra had developed a soft spot for the 'vigilante,' as she had been the victim of violent crime herself at the hands of Brian Moser. Rather than reveal herself to Lumen and Dexter, Debra told them that she was going to leave and call for backup, and they had better be gone by the time she got back. They were.<br></p>
<p>Dexter and Lumen chopped Jordan up, wrapped his body parts in plastic and dumped them in the Gulf Stream from the deck of Dexter's boat. With Dexter's help, Lumen had successfully achieved revenge by killing all of her tormentors.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135090">S5.EP12 // "The Big One"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/4-jordan-1.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/4-jordan-2.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/4-jordan-3.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/4-jordan-4.jpg" />
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/4-jordan-5.jpg" />
				</images>
				<audio src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/mp3/512_voiceover.mp3" />
				<video titleId="1159707964001" />
			</victim>
			<victim name="Rankin" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/rankin.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/rankinColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Rankin<br>
						1975 - 2010
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Well, I'm real sorry for your loss, but your dead wife can suck my d**k.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Well, I'm real sorry for your loss, but your dead wife can suck my d**k."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO RANKIN WAS:</h3>
						<p>A Jerk<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Rankin insulted Dexter on the wrong day.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>RANKIN'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>None<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Wracked with guilt over Rita's death, Dexter was fleeing Miami on his boat, Slice of Life. He stopped for fuel at a marina and encountered Rankin in the store. There were no employees there, and the angry Rankin went behind the counter himself and scrounged for the bathroom key, which was attached to a small but heavy anchor as a theft deterrent. When Rankin caught Dexter staring at him he called Dexter a retard.<br></p>
<p>Dexter tried to let it slide but couldn't. He followed Rankin into the bathroom and explained that he had just lost his wife. Rankin responded snidely with what turned out to be his last words.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter snapped, grabbed the bathroom key anchor and bludgeoned Rankin to death with it.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Unknown, but since Dexter was travelling on Slice of Life, we can assume what he did with Rankin's remains.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135079">S5.EP01 // "My Bad"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/4-Rankin.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Boyd Fowler" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/fowler.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/fowlerColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Boyd Fowler<br>
						1977 - 2010
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[You don't know what you are getting into.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"You don't know what you are getting into."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO BOYD WAS:</h3>
						<p>Sanitation Department Employee, Ex-con, Orphan, Homeowner, Self Help Practitioner, Rapist, Torturer, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Boyd was part of a serial killing gang that kidnapped, raped and tortured a series of twelve women before shoving their bodies in barrels and dumping them in a swamp.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>BOYD'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Twelve pretty young women, all blond.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter discovered blood in the back of a moving van he rented. Unable to help himself, Dexter analyzed the blood, determined it belonged to a woman who had been reported missing, and used the truck's rental records to trace the crime back to Boyd.<br></p>
<p>Dexter phoned in a dead raccoon on the side of the road and waited until Boyd came to do his job, cleaning up road kill. Dexter tailed Boyd back to his house, then followed him as he drove to a swamp and dumped a barrel into it. Dexter observed that there were several other similar barrels half-submerged in the muck. Dexter returned to the swamp later and discovered that each of the barrels contained the body of a young woman.<br></p>
<p>Dexter staged a reunion with Boyd and convinced him to take him on as his protégé. He already had a kill room all set up in a remote area, and he was planning to kill Boyd in it. But when Dexter stabbed Boyd with his M-99 syringe, Boyd acted fast and shot Dexter with a tranquilizer dart. They both ended up in the hospital.<br></p>
<p>Dexter managed to escape the ER ahead of Boyd and made his way to Boyd's house. When Boyd returned home, Dexter was waiting for him. And this time, Boyd succumbed to the M-99 without incident.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter set up a makeshift kill room in Boyd's living room. Lacking plastic wrap, he used newspaper for the walls and duct tape to secure Boyd to the kill table. He used one of Boyd's carving knives to kill him, plunging it into his chest.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Unknown.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135081">S5.EP03 // "Practically Perfect"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/4-Fowler.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Mondale" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/mondale.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/mondaleColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Dan Mendell<br>
						1974 - 2010
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[They're gonna find you, you c**t.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"They're gonna find you, you c**t."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO DAN WAS:</h3>
						<p>Pediatric Dentist, Husband, Father, Rapist, Torturer, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Dan was part of a serial killing gang that kidnapped, raped and tortured a series of twelve women before shoving their bodies in barrels and dumping them in a swamp. Lumen called Dexter for help after she shot and wounded Dan, and Dexter finished the job.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DAN'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Twelve pretty young women, all blond.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter was in the process of killing Lance Robinson when he got a frantic call from Lumen saying that she had shot Dan and didn't know what to do. Dexter stopped what he was doing and went to help her, taking along Lance Robinson's already tranquilized body.<br></p>
<p>It turned out Lumen just wounded Dan and he was able to get away. Dexter and Lumen followed the trail of blood into a warehouse. Dan and Lumen argue, and Dan tries to convince Dexter that Lumen is lying. But then they hear Dan talking on a cellphone to another member of the killing gang and Dexter learns that Lumen's horrible story is true.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>When Dan threatened Lumen, Dexter quickly snapped his neck.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>The police responded to the gunshots Lumen fired and arrived before they can dispose of the body. Acting fast, Dexter killed Lance Robinson and put his body in the same room as Dan's, staging the scene to look like a murder/suicide. This is exactly what Masuka concludes in his investigation.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135084">S5.EP06 // "Everything is Illumenated"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/4-Mendell.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Lance Robinson" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/robinson.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/robinsonColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Lance Robinson<br>
						1976 - 2010
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[You must be ten inches of pure steel.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"You must be ten inches of pure steel."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO LANCE WAS:</h3>
						<p>Homosexual, Entrapper, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Eager to get back into his regular routine of satisfying his need to kill on people who deserve it, Dexter identified Lance as the killer in four recent gay murders.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LANCE'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Four unsuspecting gay men who were looking for sex from Lance<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Dexter rented an RV and placed a personal ad that Lance answered. When Lance arrived for the tryst, Dexter shot him up with M-99 and dragged him into the RV. He wrapped Lance in plastic in preparation for the kill, but was interrupted by a phone call from Lumen. She needed Dexter's help to deal with Dan Mendell, whom Lumen had shot and wounded. Dexter reluctantly agreed to help her, and was forced to drag Lance's shrink wrapped, comatose body along for the ride.<br></p>
<p>While Dexter and Lumen were busy killing Dan Mendell, Lance awoke in the back of Dexter's car. Deb and Masuka were nearby, having responded to the gunshots Lumen fired at Dan Mendell.  Lance managed to escape and ran off in the direction of the approaching police, still naked and wrapped in plastic. Dexter chased Lance and was able to catch him just before he entered Deb and Masuka's flashlight beams.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter quietly strangled Lance with the plastic wrap from around his body before Deb and Masuka saw them.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Acting fast, Dexter put Lance's body in the same room as Dan's, staging the scene to look like a gay, auto-erotic murder/suicide. This is exactly what Masuka concludes in his investigation.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135084">S5.EP06 // "Everything is Illumenated"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/4-Robinson.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Cole Harmon" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/harmon.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/harmonColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Cole Harmon<br>
						1974 - 2010
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Huey, Dewey and Louie.]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Huey, Dewey and Louie."<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO COLE WAS:</h3>
						<p>Bodyguard, Disgraced Marine, S & M Practitioner, Accomplice, Kidnapper, Torturer, Rapist, Murderer<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Cole is the head of Jordan Chase's security, and also part of a serial killing gang that kidnapped, raped and tortured a series of twelve women before shoving their bodies in barrels and dumping them in a swamp. One of Cole's jobs was to retrieve the barrels from the swamp and dispose of them.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>COLE'S KNOWN VICTIMS:</h3>
						<p>Twelve pretty young women, all blond<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Lumen identified Cole to Dexter as a member of the gang that kidnapped, raped and tortured her. She called him 'The Suit' because he was always impeccably dressed. When Cole's truck was hit as he was transporting five body-containing barrels, he became Miami Metro's prime suspect in the Barrel Girls case.<br></p>
<p>Dexter wanted Cole for himself, so he threw off his co-workers by planting Boyd Fowler's wallet in Cole's truck.<br></p>
<p>Dexter and Lumen attended one of Jordan Chase's self-help seminars with the hope of trapping and killing Cole. Dexter booked the room adjacent to Cole's, picked the lock to the connecting door between their rooms and set his own room up as a kill room. Dexter and Lumen's plans were thwarted when Cole picked up a woman and had rough sex with her in his room as Lumen listened, horrified.<br></p>
<p>The next day, Dexter's plans to nab Cole were thwarted again when Jordan Chase spotted Dexter in his seminar audience and called him up on stage. Chase forced Dexter to talk about his wife's death in front of the audience. Meanwhile, Cole recognized Lumen in the hotel hallway and chased her to Dexter's room. Cole tried to strangle Lumen and Dexter arrived just in time to save her.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter and Lumen secured Cole to the kill table with plastic wrap. Dexter tried to get Cole to give up the names of the other members of the Barrel Girl gang, but he wouldn't. Dexter forced Cole to look at the pictures of his victims in their barrel tombs, then, as Lumen watched, he plunged a knife into Cole's chest.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter and Lumen chopped up Cole's body and Dexter carried the pieces out of the hotel in his luggage. He and Lumen then dumped the pieces in the Gulf Stream from the deck of Dexter's boat, Slice of Life. It is a cathartic experience for Lumen.<br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135086">S5.EP08 // "Take It"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/4-Harmon.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
			<victim name="Stan Liddy" polaroid="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/liddy.png" polaroidColor="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/liddyColor.png" primary="false">
				<header>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="header">
						Stan Liddy<br>
						1954 - 2010
					</div>
					]]>
				</header>
				<quote><![CDATA[Whatdya say?]]></quote>
				<body>
					<![CDATA[
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>LAST WORDS:</h3>
						<p>"Whatdya say?"<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>WHO STAN WAS:</h3>
						<p>Disgraced Cop, Freelance Private Eye, Kidnapper<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S MOTIVE:</h3>
						<p>Self-defense.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>STAN'S KNOWN VICTIMS</h3>
						<p>None<br></p>
					</div>
					<div class="pair">
						<h3>DEXTER'S TRACKING METHOD:</h3>
						<p>Stan was a dirty narcotics officer and was fired from Miami Metro in disgrace. Detective Quinn hired him on the sly to tail Dexter because he still suspected Dexter in the closed Trinity Killer case. Dexter caught on to Quinn, but didn't know about Stan.<br></p>
<p>Stan had parked a surveillance van outside of Dexter's house and Dexter found it. When Dexter approached the van to investigate, Stan tazered him, threw him in the van and drove off.<br></p>
<p>Stan drove to a secluded location by the water. It turned out Stan had surveillance pictures of Dexter and Lumen disposing of Cole Harmon's body. He threatened to expose Dexter to Quinn with the hope of getting his job back.  He called Quinn to come and meet him.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>THE KILL:</h3>
						<p>Dexter fought with Stan and despite having his wrists bound, he managed to wrest Stan's knife from him and drive it into Stan's chest, killing him. Quinn arrived as Stan was dying, and Dexter only just managed to escape detection by locking the doors and hiding in the van.<br></p>
					</div>
					<div>
						<h3>BODY DISPOSAL:</h3>
						<p>After Quinn left, Dexter got an urgent call from Lumen and didn't have time to deal with Stan's body. He took Stan's knife, laptop and the tape from his video camera and tossed them in the water, then left the corpse in the van. <br></p>
					</div>
					]]>
				</body>
				<episode>
					<a href="http://www.sho.com/site/dexter/episodes.sho?episodeid=135089">S5.EP11 // "Hop a Freighter"</a>
				</episode>
				<images>
					<img src="/assets/images/series/dexter/s6/killroom/img/slides/4-Liddy.jpg" />
				</images>
			</victim>
		</season>
	</seasons>
</feed>